Hello
hello friends welcome to your own YouTube
channel Lagi Bhi on job subject friends today
's video is going to be very important
so please watch this video till the end a
vacancy has come out it has come out from
ICICI Bank in your bank
your vacancy is going to be the
best vacancy you can
apply for it from all over India for 1 hour
I have both female candidates
if we talk about the total number of that seat
then your vacancies have been announced for very good posts
if you have seen my posts till now
then like and share them if you are
on the channel for the first time then do subscribe to the channel
so let's start the
total posts this vacancy has been
announced for approximately 6000 posts which is a very big challenge for you guys the
vacancy has been announced so
vacancies have been announced for single window operator assistant manager relationship manager customer service manager finance assistant posts
when did the online forms start you have already started filling up it has
started from 8th August yours is
September 2012  It will be filled till
September 2000, that is, if we
talk about September 2000, then the application will be filled for General OBC
candidates, there is
no fee for them, such and Asian generation
disabled candidates, you will fill this application
absolutely free, after that
how much minimum you can
check in its notification by going to its official site,
what should be your qualification, if you have done
graduation in music then you can apply for it through this
or if you are going to stay then it will be
very
good, you will get 37 thousand in this, the
best thing is that this is going to
give a permanent job, here you
can also share your experience
and it is going to
give it soon for two pregnancies,
how will the selection process be done, then
first your selection will be done,
after that your interview will be done,
then after that your correction will be done,
so in almost all the vacancies, which you
study moon i.e. your forms are filled online  There are
some such vacancies for which
those lines are filled in the Prime Honey Singh form,
then you are going to be from your original home and your
job location is of India, that is,
you belong to any region of India,
you can apply for this vacancy,
both male and female
candidates will be eligible, you can get the information by
visiting the official site of the artist
through the PDF of its notification,
if you have a PIMPL then
definitely apply for the phone, do tell us how you liked the information
in the comment section,
like the video and share it, press the bell icon
so that you do not miss any of our upcoming
betas, if you are on our channel for the
first time then definitely subscribe to Anand Channel
because we keep providing you the latest updates of the government,
Jai
Hind Jai Bharat